[
{"question": "1. Which word describes you better?", "answers": [{"response": "a.fearless", "movie": "thriller"}, {"response": "b.witty", "movie": "comedy"},{"response": "c.sensible", "movie": "drama"},{"response": "d.determined", "movie": "action"},{"response": "e.passionate", "movie": "romance"}]},
{"question":"2.Which aspect of a movie is the most important one?","answers": [{"response": "a.plot twists", "movie": "thriller"}, {"response": "b.powerful emotions", "movie": "romance"},{"response": "c.jokes", "movie": "comedy"},{"response": "d.suspense", "movie": "action"}]},
{"question":"3. Who is the best hero?","answers": [{"response": "a.Homer Simpson", "movie": "comedy"}, {"response": "b.Jack(Titanic)", "movie": "romance"},{"response": "c.Augustus Waters", "movie": "drama"},{"response": "d.Princess Leia", "movie": "action"},{"response": "e.Rambo", "movie": "thriller"}]},
{"question":"4. What\"s the best time to watch a movie?","answers": [{"response": "a.at sunset/sunrise", "movie": "drama"}, {"response": "b.anytime", "movie": "comedy"},{"response": "c.afternoon", "movie": "action"},{"response": "d.2 AM", "movie": "thriller"}]},
{"question":"5. Which of these movies appeals more to you?","answers": [{"response": "a.The Notebook", "movie": "romance"}, {"response": "b.Titanic", "movie": "drama"},{"response": "c.Star Wars", "movie": "action"},{"response": "d.The Nightmare on Elm Street", "movie": "thriller"},{"response": "e.American Pie", "movie": "comedy"}]},
{"question":"6. If you could visit any of these places, which one would you choose?","answers": [{"response": "a.Paris", "movie": "romance"}, {"response": "b.Las Vegas", "movie": "comedy"},{"response": "c.A haunted mansion", "movie": "thriller"},{"response": "d.Sicily", "movie": "action"}]},
{"question":"7. What kind of dreams do you have?","answers": [{"response": "a.Fighting", "movie": "action"}, {"response": "b.Partying", "movie": "comedy"},{"response": "c.Being on a date", "movie": "romance"},{"response": "d.Running", "movie": "thriller"}]},
{"question":"8. Do you like a happy ending?","answers": [{"response": "a.Yes", "movie": "comedy"}, {"response": "b.No", "movie": "thriller"}]},
{"question":"9. How does your average movie night look like?","answers": [{"response": "a.Having a good laugh", "movie": "comedy"}, {"response": "b.Alone with tissues", "movie": "drama"},{"response": "c.Day-dreaming", "movie": "romance"},{"response": "d.Enjoying something high-energy", "movie": "action"},{"response": "e.Trying to scare myself", "movie": "thriller"}]},
{"question":"10. What\"s your favorite color?","answers": [{"response": "a.pink", "movie": "romance"}, {"response": "b.black", "movie": "thriller"},{"response": "c.red", "movie": "action"},{"response": "d.light purple", "movie": "drama"},{"response": "e.blue", "movie": "comedy"}]}
]
